Greetings and welcome to my end of course.
Let me give you a quick introduction as to who I am.
If you don't know already my name is Nathan house and I'm the CEO and founder of the cyber security
company station X. And I'll be on Struktur throughout this comprehensive and Emap course over 24 years
experience in cybersecurity and I've advised many of the largest companies in the world.
Sure that's good.
A multi-million and even multi-billion pound projects I provide security guidance to companies such
as Vodafone BP visa the London 2012 Olympics and a number of banks and financial institutions plus many
other companies.
I was a security lead on a number of the UK mobile banking apps so if you live in the UK you may well
have an app on your phone that I have helped secure.
I have many security qualifications including susp cism CSA SC among others over the years.
I spoke on a number of conferences develop free security tools and discovered serious security vulnerabilities
in leading applications as a security educator.
I have sold over 50000 courses which were all highly reviewed and excellently rated of a popular cybersecurity
blog and I currently have over 60000 active Twitter followers who listen to my advice.
So in theory I should know what I'm talking about when it comes to network security.
Ethical hacking cyber security alerts have just been getting away with it all these years.
It's never been more important than it is today to maintain good security and to lie unmap helps in
that task and extremely passionate about helping you learn and achieve your goals.
And I'm very excited to be here to teach you.
If you have any questions please just ask.
I'm here to help.