Let's start by giving you a quick introduction as to why and map is and map short for network mapper
is a free and open source command line tool for Network Discovery and security assessment is used by
ethical hackers penetration testers systems administrators black hackers and anyone in fact who wants
to understand more about the devices on a given network is also often called a network scanner or a
port scanner because it scans for open ports on devices.
But it has much more functionality than just a simple port on network scanner and port scanning.
If you're not familiar with what that means what that term is.
Well this will tell the user of the scanner what ports are open on the scan devices and therefore what
services are running such as as you can see here we've got port 22 open so we know on this device which
happens to be 1 9 2 don't want to say I don't want one that is potentially S-sh and it's giving us some
version information here so we can say that this is S-sh or it could be poor 80 and it could be hasty
TPA web server or 53 which is a DNS server.
So that is what ports does does doors and map.
It determines whether the host is up and it determines what the host is running on it and it can do
that across multiple different domain names and IP addresses and map users rural IP packets specially
crafted in order to determine this.
So it tells you as I've said what houses are available on a given network what services as we can see
here the services like the application name and the version the House that are available in this instance
we can see one or the 1:06 I don't want as I've said and potentially what operating system we can see
here Linux we can see here the Linux kernel and depending on the scan what type of packet filtering
firewalls are in use and many of the characteristics can be deemed using unmap and that also is a powerful
scripting capability.
It allows users to write and share scripts using the alleyway louer programming language to automate
a wide variety of networking tasks including things like network discovery more sophisticated version
detection and vulnerability detection.
It can be used scripting can be used for vulnerability exploitation and even brute forcing.
Emma was designed to rapidly scan large networks but works fine against single host to chat rooms on
all major operating systems and official Minories are avail for Linux Windows and Mac OS X to name a
few.
In addition to the classic command line and map executable we can see the output here and map Swee also
includes a GUI called Zend map which you can see here for a graphical interface to unmap all of which
were going to go through on this course.
So that was your quick introduction to encapsulate.
Carry on.